<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Swiftpedia</string>
    <string name="album_name">Album Name</string>
    <string name="release_date">Release Date</string>
    <string name="short_description">Short Description</string>
    <string name="song_list">Song List</string>
    <string name="debut_album">Debut Album</string>
    <string name="fearless_album">Fearless</string>
    <string name="speak_now_album">Speak Now</string>
    <string name="red_album">Red</string>
    <string name="the1989_album">1989</string>
    <string name="reputation_album">Reputation</string>
    <string name="lover_album">Lover</string>
    <string name="folklore_album">Folklore</string>
    <string name="evermore_album">Evermore</string>
    <string name="midnight_album">Midnight</string>
    <string name="ttpd_album">The Tortured Poets Department</string>
    <string name="main">Main Menu</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="profileName">Rizky Aditya</string>
    <string name="email_address">Rizky.aditya41119@gmail.com</string>
    <string-array name="album_names">
        <item>Debut Album</item>
        <item>Fearless</item>
        <item>Speak Now</item>
        <item>Red</item>
        <item>1989</item>
        <item>Reputation</item>
        <item>Lover</item>
        <item>Folklore</item>
        <item>Evermore</item>
        <item>Midnight</item>
        <item>The Tortured Poets Department</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="release_date">
        <item>October 24, 2006</item>
        <item>November 11, 2008</item>
        <item>October 25, 2010</item>
        <item>October 22, 2012</item>
        <item>October 27, 2014</item>
        <item>November 10, 2017</item>
        <item>August 23, 2019</item>
        <item>July 24, 2020</item>
        <item>December 11, 2020</item>
        <item>October 21, 2022</item>
        <item>April 19, 2024</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="short_description">
        <item> Taylor Swift eponymous debut studio album was released on October 24, 2006,
            through Big Machine Records. Swift, who signed a record deal in 2005,
            wrote or co-wrote every song on the album, with Liz Rose contributing to most co-written tracks.
            Produced by Nathan Chapman, the album blends country and pop styles, exploring themes of romantic
            relationships, some of which Swift observed before experiencing them
            firsthand during her freshman year of high school.</item>
        <item>"Fearless" is Taylor Swift second studio album, released on November 11, 2008,
            via Big Machine Records. Swift wrote or co-wrote all thirteen tracks,
            many penned while touring as the opening act for various country artists.
            She collaborated with writers like Liz Rose, Hillary Lindsey, Colbie Caillat, and John Rich.
            Notably, Swift also co-produced the album with Nathan Chapman, marking her debut
            as a record producer.</item>
        <item>Speak Now is Taylor Swift third studio album, released on
            October 25, 2010, by Big Machine Records. Swift, along with Nathan Chapman,
            handled production from 2008 to 2010. The album, written entirely by Swift,
            follows her previous work but incorporates a bigger pop-rock sound.
            It explores themes of love, romance, and heartbreak. The deluxe edition includes
            bonus tracks and acoustic versions, with a wider US release in 2012.
        </item>
        <item>Red is Taylor Swift fourth studio album, released on October 22, 2012,
            by Big Machine Records. The title reflects Swift turbulent emotions during its creation
            exploring fading romance. To explore new sounds, Swift worked with various producers
            including Max Martin and Shellback. The album blends pop, country, and rock, incorporating
            elements like arena rock, Britrock, and dance-pop. Though promoted as country,
            it was widely considered a pop record. It spawned seven singles
            including "We Are Never Ever Getting Back Together" and "I Knew You Were Trouble."
        </item>
        <item>"1989" is Taylor Swift fifth studio album, released on October 27, 2014,
            by Big Machine Records. Departing from her country roots, Swift embraced 1980s synth-pop
            for a pop recalibration. The album title, reflecting her birth year, symbolizes a
            new artistic chapter. Max Martin, co-executive producer, helmed production with contributors
            like Shellback, Jack Antonoff, and Ryan Tedder. Synth-pop elements dominate,
            marking a departure from Swift acoustic style. Lyrically, the album delves into
            failed romance from a lighthearted angle, expanding on Swift autobiographical
            storytelling.
        </item>
        <item> reputation is Taylor Swift sixth studio album, released on November 10, 2017,
            under Big Machine Records. Crafted in response to media scrutiny following "1989,"
            Swift drew inspiration from publicized disputes and relationships collaborating primarily
            with Jack Antonoff, Max Martin, and Shellback to create an electro pop and RNB record
            infused with hip hop, trap, and EDM elements. Eschewing traditional promotion, Swift cleared
            her website and social media accounts, generating significant attention.
            Despite mixed initial reviews, "reputation" achieved commercial success, becoming Swift
            fourth consecutive album to sell one million copies in its first week in the US, s
            pending four weeks atop the Billboard 200, and earning triple platinum certification.
            It received critical recognition, earning a Grammy nomination for Best Pop Vocal Album,
            with retrospective reviews highlighting its experimental nature and artistic evolution.</item>
        <item>"Lover" is Taylor Swift seventh studio album, released on August 23, 2019,
            under Republic Records, marking her first album after departing from Big Machine Records.
            Produced with Jack Antonoff, Joel Little, Louis Bell, and Frank Dukes, the album is described
            by Swift as a "love letter to love," delving into themes of infatuation, commitment,
            and societal issues like LGBT rights and feminism. Its production blends
            1980s-inspired electropop, pop rock, and synth-pop with elements of country, folk, and funk.
            Despite some criticism for its wide-ranging musical styles, "Lover" received praise for
            its emotional depth and free-spirited sound upon release.
            It spawned four successful singles in 2019 and was Swift sixth consecutive Billboard 200
            number-one album in the US, earning triple platinum certification. While retrospective
            reviews note its eclectic nature, they generally uphold Swift mature
            songwriting while acknowledging mixed results in sound cohesion. The album received Grammy
            and American Music Award nominations, solidifying its impact in Swift discography.
        </item>
        <item>"Folklore" is Taylor Swift surprise eighth studio album, released on July 24, 2020,
            via Republic Records amidst the COVID-19 pandemic. Created during quarantine, Swift collaborated
            virtually with producers Aaron Dessner and Jack Antonoff, crafting mellow ballads exploring themes
            of escapism, empathy, and nostalgia. Departing from her upbeat pop style, the album delves into indie
            folk, alternative rock, and electro-acoustic sounds, featuring tracks like "Cardigan" and "Exile"
            with Bon Iver. "Folklore" received widespread acclaim for its emotional depth and poetic lyricism,
            topping charts globally and earning platinum certifications in multiple countries.
            It became Swift seventh number-one album in the US and the best-selling album of 2020.
            The album won Album of the Year at the 63rd Annual Grammy Awards, marking Swift historic
            third win in the category.Rolling Stone included "Folklore" in their list of the
            500 Greatest Albums of All Time.</item>
        <item>Evermore is Taylor Swift surprise ninth studio album released on
            December 11, 2020, via Republic Records, emerged as a spontaneous collaboration with Aaron Dessner,
            following their work on "Folklore." Inspired by cottage core aesthetics, "Evermore"
            is considered a sister album to "Folklore," featuring alternative rock,
            indie folk, and chamber pop styles with guest appearances by Bon Iver, Haim, and the National.
            The album, acclaimed for its experimental production and nuanced storytelling,
            explores themes of love, marriage, and grief through impressionistic narratives.
            It topped charts globally, with "Willow" becoming Swift seventh Billboard Hot 100 number-one song.
            "Evermore" received a Grammy nomination for Album of the Year at the 64th Annual Grammy Awards,
            solidifying Swift continued impact on the music industry.</item>
        <item>"Midnights" marks Taylor Swift tenth studio album, released on October 21, 2022,
            by Republic Records. Conceptualized as a reflection on sleepless nights, the album delves
            into themes of regret, self-criticism, and infatuation through autobiographical songwriting.
            Produced with Jack Antonoff, the standard edition features subdued electronic sounds blending
            synth-pop, electropop, and dream pop elements. Additional tracks on the surprise-released
            3am Edition were produced by Aaron Dessner. "Midnights" debuted atop the Billboard 200,
            becoming Swift 11th consecutive number-one album and the best-selling album of 2022.
            Lead single "Anti-Hero" propelled Swift to monopolize the Billboard Hot 100 top 10.
            Critics praised Swift songwriting and the album restrained production
            though some noted familiar influences. "Midnights" received multiple platinum certifications
            and won Album of the Year at the 66th Annual Grammy Awards, solidifying Swift
            continued influence and popularity.</item>
        <item>"The Tortured Poets Department" is Taylor Swift upcoming eleventh studio album,
            scheduled for release on April 19, 2024, via Republic Records. Swift announced the album at
            the 66th Annual Grammy Awards in February 2024, following her win for Best Pop Vocal Album
            with "Midnights" (2022). Conceived shortly after completing "Midnights," Swift developed
            the album during the Eras Tour (2023–2024), describing it as her "lifeline" record driven by
            imperative songwriting. Featuring sixteen songs, the album includes collaborations with
            rapper Post Malone and indie rock band Florence and the Machine, with bonus tracks
            available on physical formats.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="debut_album_song">
        <item>Tim McGraw</item>
        <item>Picture To Burn</item>
        <item>Teardrops On My Guitar</item>
        <item>A Place in The World</item>
        <item>Cold As You</item>
        <item>The Outside</item>
        <item>Tied Together with a smile</item>
        <item>Stay Beautiful</item>
        <item>Shouldve Said No</item>
        <item>Our Song</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fearless_album_song">
        <item>Fearless</item>
        <item>Fifteen</item>
        <item>Love Story</item>
        <item>Hey Stephen</item>
        <item>White Horse</item>
        <item>Young Belong With Me</item>
        <item>Breathe (feat.Colbie Calliat)</item>
        <item>Tell Me Why</item>
        <item>Youre Not Sorry</item>
        <item>The Way I Loved You</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="speak_now_song">
        <item>Mine</item>
        <item>Sparks Fly</item>
        <item>Back To December</item>
        <item>Speak Now</item>
        <item>Dear John</item>
        <item>Mean</item>
        <item>Enchanted</item>
        <item>Better Than Revenge</item>
        <item>Haunted</item>
        <item>Long Live</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="red_song">
        <item>State Of Grace</item>
        <item>Red</item>
        <item>I Knew You Were Trouble</item>
        <item>All Too Well (10 Minutes Version)</item>
        <item>22</item>
        <item>We Are Never Ever Getting Back Together</item>
        <item>Everything Has Changed</item>
        <item>Come Back...Be Here</item>
        <item>Better Man</item>
        <item>Ronan</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="the1989_song">
        <item>Blank Space</item>
        <item>Style</item>
        <item>Out Of The Woods</item>
        <item>All You Had To Do Was Stay</item>
        <item>Shake It Off</item>
        <item>I Wish You Would</item>
        <item>Wildest Dreams</item>
        <item>I Know Places</item>
        <item>Is It Over Now?</item>
        <item>Now That We Dont Talk</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="reputation_song">
        <item>Ready For It</item>
        <item>Endgame</item>
        <item>Look What You Made Me Do</item>
        <item>Delicate</item>
        <item>I Did Something Bad</item>
        <item>King Of My Heart</item>
        <item>Georgous</item>
        <item>Getaway Car</item>
        <item>Dress</item>
        <item>Dont Blame Me</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="lover_song">
        <item>I Forgot That You Existed</item>
        <item>Cruel Summer</item>
        <item>Lover</item>
        <item>The Man</item>
        <item>The Archer</item>
        <item>I Think He Knows</item>
        <item>Miss Americana and The Heartbreak Prince</item>
        <item>Me!</item>
        <item>Cornelia Street</item>
        <item>You Need To Calm Down</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="folklore_song">
        <item>the 1</item>
        <item>cardigan</item>
        <item>the last great american dynasty</item>
        <item>exile (feat.Bon Iver)</item>
        <item>my tears ricochet</item>
        <item>mirrorball</item>
        <item>seven</item>
        <item>august</item>
        <item>betty</item>
        <item>illicit affairs</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="evermore_song">
        <item>willow</item>
        <item>champagne problems</item>
        <item>gold rush</item>
        <item>tis the damn season</item>
        <item>tolerate it</item>
        <item>no body, no crime (feat.HAIM)</item>
        <item>dorothea</item>
        <item>ivy</item>
        <item>evermore</item>
        <item>coney island (feat. The National)</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="midnight_song">
        <item>lavender haze</item>
        <item>maroon</item>
        <item>anti-hero</item>
        <item>your on your own, kid</item>
        <item>midnight rain</item>
        <item>labyrinth</item>
        <item>bejeweled</item>
        <item>question?</item>
        <item>karma</item>
        <item>mastermind</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ttpd_song">
        <item>"Fortnight" (featuring Post Malone)</item>
        <item>"The Tortured Poets Department"</item>
        <item>"My Boy Only Breaks His Favorite Toys"</item>
        <item>"Down Bad"</item>
        <item>"So Long, London"</item>
        <item>"But Daddy I Love Him"</item>
        <item>"Fresh Out the Slammer"</item>
        <item>"Florida!!!" (featuring Florence and the Machine)</item>
        <item>"Guilty as Sin?"</item>
        <item>"Who Afraid of Little Old Me?"</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="album_photo">
        <item>@drawable/debut</item>
        <item>@drawable/fearless</item>
        <item>@drawable/speak_now</item>
        <item>@drawable/red</item>
        <item>@drawable/the1989</item>
        <item>@drawable/reputation</item>
        <item>@drawable/lover</item>
        <item>@drawable/folklore</item>
        <item>@drawable/evermore</item>
        <item>@drawable/midnight</item>
        <item>@drawable/tortured_poets</item>
    </integer-array>

</resources>